





Summary

Last Active: 19-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Dedicated & focused professional, offering over 9 years of decent exposure in capacities for the role Business analyst. Displayed paramount efforts; recognized as Critical Resource and received appreciations mails from clients for completing work on time with utmost quality. Selected by leadership and peer group to spearhead client base at Doha Qatar as an International BA to work on new application enhancement.

Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Active member of Change management team TCS and handled various epic as per client requirements using agile methodology, Scrum Planning and Business Backlog review. Expert in identifying the requirements and also in finding the system requirements.

Certified trained professional with IMARTICUS learning on SAP Change Management Pro-degree - Business Analysis. Expert understanding of SDLC processes and Agile flavoured development methodologies (Waterfall, Scrum, Agile Framework, Principles).

Work Experience

Hexaware Technologies as Business Analyst

Apr 2019 to Till Date

Managing Client requirements (Commercial Cards), Trigger forecast for Live working hours, leading meetings & knowledge

sharing, stake holder interactions

Analyzing process flow on use cases and recording required updates on user stories that needs to updated for effective work

flow

Review whether the controls are been placed over transactions by processing various quality checks on different reviews for

monetary and non-monetary services to validate that stake holders who had impact of processing are processing as per the

guidelines

Creating framework for BCP plan to manage BAU at the fullest as per client requirements at critical lockdown COMD-19 situations

Conducting the project meetings successfully by coordinating all users

Leveraging skills by implementing new ideas in current workflow of Cards Operations for EMEA region

Tata Consultancy Services as Senior Analyst

Mar 2014 to Apr 2019

Role: Business analyst

Managing stake holders & Client requirement (Operation Risk Management), Trigger forecast for Live working hours, leading

leading washing 9 languages sharing. Training poors on process 9 skill development Data on pluma MC forecast at least

Important

Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld.

meetings & knowledge sharing , Training pears on process & skill development, Data on volume ivi⊳ iorecast, stake holder

interactions

Tracking Impact analysis and estimating the efforts that are required by different stake holders.

Actively Participated in internal presentations, Clarified issues with developers during efforts to validate designs and functional

specifications, Helped the developing teams in mapping the data,

Defined architectural components by creating professional model on vital controls that needs to be placed, analyzing and

providing results on critical processes

Leveraging skills in working on Forex received from different teams within the ODC related to Qr., USD, GBP, EUR, and Test

samples by booking the entries for the same

Interviewed the stakeholders and preparation of documents also managed relationship with programmers and bridged communication between end users and development team

Conducted the project meetings with all users, technical staff

Supported in QA testing and active participation in reconciliation, audit sampling & filling.

Adhering compliance with rules and regulations of the bank including latest circulars & notifications; thus following the process / procedure of the bank

Showcasing active participation through social management group regularizing of daily activities within organization: "Safety

Champion of TCS safety management of Spencer branch"

Highlights:

Received appreciations mails from clients for completing work on time

Bagged the opportunity to work with client base @ Qatar as an International deputation

Recognized as Critical Resource' by the organization considering the experience & work knowledge

ICICI Bank Ltd. as Customer Service Officer

Nov 2011 to Nov 2013

Engaged in managing Fixed Deposit, FD, RD, Gold, Debit Cards, NEFT, RTGS, Cash, Statement of Accounts, Life Insurance,

Mutual Funds, and so on

Managing complete processing of in-house cheque transactions for day in and out circulation of funds from one account to

another CB account

Assisted the team for better client servicing which included providing guidelines for over-the-counter, interacting with customers, obtaining their feedback, implementing the feedback in the system, and so on

Imparting trainings for performing investment activities like reconciliation of stocks, fund transfer requests and acknowledging

queries regarding account statements

Collaborated with co-operative banks; analysed & verified inward & outward clearing for seamless operations

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Com (Commerce) from DG Vaishnava College, Madras University in 2011

PG: PG Diploma (Banking Operations -IFBI) from NIIT in 2012

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

MBA

SAP Change Management Pro-degree -Business Analysis

Diploma in PC Professional (PCP)

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Methodologies UML, Waterfall	
AGILE	

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Marathi				
tamil				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved @ 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.